<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>my migraines on my migraine</title><link>https://lexahl.github.io/migraine/</link><description>Recent content in my migraines on my migraine</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lexahl.github.io/migraine/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>resources</title><link>https://lexahl.github.io/migraine/resources/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lexahl.github.io/migraine/resources/</guid><description>migraine resources There are many great migraine resources and lists that organisations and communities have created for migraine, but these are what has worked for me. join a community What helped me the most was joining a community to talk about migraine. From small things like memes and how a can of coke can speed up the effects of triptans, to more significant conversations like how to come to terms with the idea that migraine might never get better, knowing there are others out there that have similar experiences has helped me a lot.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://lexahl.github.io/migraine/about/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lexahl.github.io/migraine/about/</guid><description>about this project This project is feminist because it is acknowledgements (alphabetical orders) This project has been developed with the guidance and support of Florence, Jo, Olu, and Yasmine. Thank your for sharing your practice and expertise with me, and thank you for your encouragement and patience. Another thank you to Kes, Mathilda, Peaks and Yifan for your kindness and community throughout the term. "We aren't meant to know everything, that is why we have each other.</description></item><item><title>chatbot</title><link>https://lexahl.github.io/migraine/chatbot/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lexahl.github.io/migraine/chatbot/</guid><description>chatbot Scroll down to start the conversation. The chatbot is not accessible for screenreaders and could be challenging for some users. Click here for a plain text file of the conversation. I don't need to explain this to you, but I want to. I know you can't see my migraine attacks, so I guess it can be hard to understand. I have borne the labour of explaining my migraine attacks for nine years now, and I am often too tired to have this conversation anymore.</description></item></channel></rss>